winscp.net 2018-11-05

# WinSCP Privacy Policy :: WinSCP

Documentation » About WinSCP » 

  * What information do we collect?
    * Visiting winscp.net
    * Installing WinSCP application
    * Using WinSCP application
  * What do we use your information for?
  * How do we protect your information?
  * Do we use cookies?
  * Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
  * Third party links
  * California online privacy protection act compliance
  * Your consent
  * Warrant canary
  * Changes to our Privacy policy

_Advertisement_

## What information do we collect?

We can collect information from you when you visit our site, install or use WinSCP application. People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. 

### Visiting winscp.net

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or location. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

After donating to WinSCP, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or donation entry details. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy policy. Users may opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies by visiting the DoubleClick opt-out page. 

### Installing WinSCP application

When installing WinSCP, we might collect anonymous information about the number of initiated and finished installations per geo-location and language. No private information is collected. WinSCP installer might offer you to install a third party application along with WinSCP, in such a case we collect also statistics for its installations. Note that before deciding to install any third party application, you are required to agree to its separate and independent Terms of use and Privacy policy. 

### Using WinSCP application

When using WinSCP application, we might collect anonymous WinSCP usage statistics. You may, however, opt-out from providing WinSCP usage statistics or from WinSCP automatic check for application updates. 

_Advertisement_

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * **To improve our website and our application** (we continually strive to improve our offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * **To process transactions** (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

## How do we protect your information?

We use PayPal to process your payments. PayPal offers the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Transport Layer Security (TLS) or Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Please refer also to PayPal Privacy policy for details. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes, on winscp.net we use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

_Advertisement_

## California online privacy protection act compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

All registered users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the forum and going to the _Profile_ page. 

## Your consent

By using our site or installing or using WinSCP, you consent to our Privacy policy. 

## Warrant canary

We have not placed any backdoors into our software and have not received any requests for doing so. Pay close attention to any modifications to the previous sentence. 

Learn about [Warrant canary](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Warrant_canary "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Warrant_canary"). 

## Changes to our Privacy policy

If we decide to change our Privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on **2015-11-15**. 

— [WinSCP team](https://winscp.net/ "https://winscp.net/")

_This policy is based on[Free Privacy Policy Generator](https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/ "https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/")._
  *[TLS]: Transport Layer Security
  *[SSL]: Secure Sockets Layer
